Midtown Galleries
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Administrative Correspondence, 1927-1989, undated, Series 1:; (51 linear ft.)
  - General Correspondence, 1932-1983, undated, 1.1:
    - STONE, HERB-STONY (Reel 5369, Frame 862-881)
    - Stookey, Donald B., 1971-1982 (Reel 5369, Frame 883-910)
    - STOP-STORK (Reel 5369, Frame 882; 911-914)
    - Storm King Art Center, 1966-1975 (Reel 5369, Frame 915-930)
    - STOU-STR (Reel 5369, Frame 931-1002)
    - Strawn Art Gallery (see: David Strawn Art Gallery) (Reel 5369)
    - STUA-STUDIO H... (Reel 5369, Frame 1003-1020)
    - Studio Museum in Harlem, 1977-1978 (Reel 5369, Frame 1021-1062)
    - STUM-SUMI (Reel 5369, Frame 1141-1188)
    - Summit Art Association, 1949-1983 (Reel 5369, Frame 1189-1210)
    - SUMMIT G...-SUT (Reel 5369, Frame 1211-1261)
    - SWA-SWEEN (Reel 5369, Frame 1262-1289)
    - Sweet Briar College, 1939-1950 (Reel 5369, Frame 1290-1434)
    - SWET-SWI (Reel 5369, Frame 1435-1455)
    - Swiss Dealers (see: German and Swiss Dealers) (Reel 5369)
    - Swope Art Gallery, 1941-1942 (Reel 5369, Frame 1456-1546)
    - Swope Art Gallery, cont., 1943-1967 (Reel 5370, Frame 5-182)
    - SYD (Reel 5370, Frame 184-186)
    - Syracuse Museum, 1937-1955 (Reel 5370, Frame 187-245)
    - Syracuse University, 1963-1984 (Reel 5370, Frame 246-297)
    - SYT (Reel 5370, Frame 298-300)
    - SZE-SZI (Reel 5370, Frame 301-329)
    - TAB (Reel 5370, Frame 330-335)
    - Tacoma Art League, 1948-1949 (Reel 5370, Frame 336-363)
    - TACOMA P...-TAF (Reel 5370, Frame 364-368)
    - Tahir Gallery, 1946-1977 (Reel 5370, Frame 369-445)
    - TAK-TAMI (Reel 5370, Frame 446-501)
    - Tampa Art Institute, 1945-1956 (Reel 5370, Frame 502-564)
    - TAMPA B...-TAZ (Reel 5370, Frame 565-665)
    - TEA-TELE (Reel 5370, Frame 666-689)
    - Telfair Academy of Arts and Sciences, 1941-1957 (Reel 5370, Frame 690-812)
    - TELL (Reel 5370, Frame 813-817)
    - TEMPLE, A.-TEMPLE U... (Reel 5370, Frame 818-890)
    - TEN-TENA (Reel 5370, Frame 891-893)
    - TENNESSEE F...-TENNESSEE S... (Reel 5370, Frame 894-913)
    - Tennessee, University of [Chattanooga], 1975 (Reel 5370, Frame 914-921)
    - Tennessee, University of [Knoxville], 1944-1974 (Reel 5370, Frame 922-965)
    - TENNESSEE V... (Reel 5370, Frame 965-066)
    - Tennis in Art, 1969-1976 (Reel 5370, Frame 967-1004)
    - TENNY-TERRE (Reel 5370, Frame 1005-1010)
    - Terry Art Institute, 1948-1955 (Reel 5370, Frame 1011-1089)
    - TER W-TEXAC (Reel 5370, Frame 1090-1105)
    - TEXAS A...-TEXAS S... (Reel 5370, Frame 1106-1122)
    - Texas Technological College, 1955-1975 (Reel 5370, Frame 1123-1153)
    - Texas, University of, 1944-1950 (Reel 5370, Frame 1154-1170)
    - Texas Western College, 1940-1960 (Reel 5370, Frame 1171-1251)
    - TEZ-THOMPSON, G. (Reel 5370, Frame 1252-1309)
    - Thompson, J. Walter, 1939-1976 (Reel 5370, Frame 1310-1447)
    - THOMPSON, JANE-TIL (Reel 5370, Frame 1448-1526)
    - Time, Inc., 1937-1938 (Reel 5370, Frame 1527-1552)
    - Time, Inc., cont. (see also: Fortune and Life), 1938-1975 (Reel 5371, Frame 5-256)
    - TIMES-TOC (Reel 5371, Frame 257-315)
    - TOD-TOLEDO B... (Reel 5371, Frame 316-356)
    - Toledo Museum of Art, 1934-1977 (Reel 5371, Frame 357-703)
    - TOM-TOP (Reel 5371, Frame 740-719)
    - Topeka Art Guild, 1944-1954 (Reel 5371, Frame 720-750)
    - TOR-TOWL (Reel 5371, Frame 751-773)
    - Town and Country, 1937-1970 (Reel 5371, Frame 774-812)
    - TOWNE-TRANK (Reel 5371, Frame 813-859)
    - Transamerica Corp., 1972-1974 (Reel 5371, Frame 860-893)
    - Transportation, 1938-1942 (Reel 5371, Frame 894-916)
    - TRANSW-TRI (Reel 5371, Frame 917-988)
    - TRL-TUC (Reel 5371, Frame 989-1031)
    - Tudor City Gallery, 1933-1935 (Reel 5371, Frame 1032-1046)
    - TUE-TUP (Reel 5371, Frame 1047-1116)
    - TUR-TY (Reel 5371, Frame 1117-1177)
    - UG-UNIO (Reel 5371, Frame 1178-1224)
    - UNITED A...-UNITED NATIONS H... (Reel 5371, Frame 1225-1291)
    - UNITED NATIONS I... (Reel 5371, Frame 1292-1334)
    - UNITED NE...-UNITED P... (Reel 5371, Frame 1335-1344)
    - United Service Organizations [USO], 1942-1943 (Reel 5371, Frame 1345-1583)
    - United Service Organizations [USO], cont., 1942-1946, 1962 (Reel 5372, Frame 5-124)
    - UNITED STATES D...-UNITED STATES H... (Reel 5372, Frame 125-176)
    - United States Department of State (see: State Department) (Reel 5372)
    - United States Information Agency (USIA), 1955-1975 (Reel 5372, Frame 177-247)
    - UNITED STATES INT...-UNITED STATES Y... (Reel 5372, Frame 248-276)
    - UNITED V...-UNIVERSITY C... (Reel 5372, Frame 277-317)
    - UNIVERSITY M... (Reel 5372, Frame 368)
    - UNIVERSITY OF... (Reel 5372, Frame 318-367)
    - UNIVERSITY P...-UNT (Reel 5372, Frame 369-378)
    - Upjohn Company (see also: McAdams, William Douglas), 1944-1962 (Reel 5372, Frame 379-629)
    - UPT-UT (Reel 5372, Frame 630-696)
    - USO (see: United Services Organizations) (Reel 5372)
    - VAG-VAN (Reel 5372, Frame 697-739)
    - VAN A...-VAN D... (Reel 5372, Frame 740-765)
    - Van Gelder, Jane, 1961-1963 (Reel 5372, Frame 766-806)
    - VAN H...-VANDERBILT, A. (Reel 5372, Frame 807-833)
    - Vanderbilt University, 1976-1978 (Reel 5372, Frame 834-858)
    - VANDERV-VAU (Reel 5372, Frame 859-903)
    - VEN-VERI (Reel 5372, Frame 904-942)
    - VERMONT C...-VERMONT U... (Reel 5372, Frame 943-977)
    - VIC-VIRGINIA L... (Reel 5372, Frame 978-1014)
    - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1937-1942 (Reel 5372, Frame 1015-1099)
    - Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, cont., 1943-1981 (Reel 5373, Frame 5-380)
    - Virginia Polytechnic Institute, 1961-1976 (Reel 5373, Frame 381-404)
    - VIRGINIA W...-VU (Reel 5373, Frame 405-478)
    - WAB-WAC (Reel 5373, Frame 479-558)
    - Waddell, Chauncey, 1957-1977 (Reel 5373, Frame 559-578)
    - Wadsworth Athenaeum, 1943-1963 (Reel 5373, Frame 579-693)
    - WAG (Reel 5373, Frame 694-710)
    - Wake Forest University, 1965-1981 (Reel 5373, Frame 711-746)
    - WAKEL-WAKO (Reel 5373, Frame 747-759)
    - Walbridge, Norton S., 1963-1973 (Reel 5373, Frame 780-810)
    - WALC-WALD (Reel 5373, Frame 811-850)
    - Walker Art Center, 1943-1981 (Reel 5373, Frame 851-964)
    - WALKER, G...-WALKER, S... (Reel 5373, Frame 965-1001)
    - Wall, Inga [Heck], 1959-1976 (Reel 5373, Frame 1002-1033)
    - WALL, P.-WALP (Reel 5373, Frame 1034-1053)
    - WALS-WALTON, J. (Reel 5373, Frame 1054-1091)
    - Walton Walk Galleries (Maurice Sternberg Galleries), 1951-1960 (Reel 5373, Frame 1092-1141)
    - WALW-WARB (Reel 5373, Frame 1142-1179)
    - WARB, cont.-WARS (Reel 5374, Frame 5-47)
    - Warner, Keith (see: Kewar Co.) (Reel 5374)
    - WASC-WASHBURN C.L. (Reel 5374, Frame 48-51)
    - Washburn College (Washburn Municipal University), 1941-1971 (Reel 5374, Frame 52-109)
    - WASHE (Reel 5374, Frame 110-111)
    - WASHINGTON AND...-WASHINGTON CE... (Reel 5374, Frame 112-129)
    - Washington County [Md.] Museum, 1940-1968 (Reel 5374, Frame 130-173)
    - WASHINGTON H...-WASHINGTON SC... (Reel 5374, Frame 174-183)
    - Washington State University, 1935-1974 (Reel 5374, Frame 184-198)
    - Washington University [St. Louis], 1948-1972 (Reel 5374, Frame 199-225)
    - WASHINGTON W...-WATKINS, F. (Reel 5374, Frame 226-282)
    - Watkins Institute, 1945-1948 (Reel 5374, Frame 254-282)
    - WATL-WATSON, T. (Reel 5374, Frame 283-291)
    - Watson-Guptill Publication, 1958-1982 (Reel 5374, Frame 292-335)
    - WATT-WEAR (Reel 5374, Frame 336-370)
    - Weatherspoon Art Gallery, 1966-1973 (Reel 5374, Frame 371-416)
    - WEATHERW-WEE (Reel 5374, Frame 417-468)
    - WEG-WEING (Reel 5374, Frame 469-536)
    - WEINS (Reel 5374, Frame 537-566)
    - Weintraub, Mr. and Mrs. S. A., 1962-1974 (Reel 5374, Frame 567-610)
    - WEIS-WELLS, A. (Reel 5374, Frame 611-657)
    - Wells, Charles E., 1958-1973 (Reel 5374, Frame 658-683)
    - WELLS, CHE...-WER (Reel 5374, Frame 684-738)
    - WESC-WESS (Reel 5374, Frame 739-787)
    - WEST, A.-WEST, E. (Reel 5374, Frame 788-807)
    - WEST, J.-WEST., R. (Reel 5374, Frame 821-844)
    - West Virginia Pulp and Paper, 1949-1965 (Reel 5374, Frame 845-874)
    - WEST VIRGINIA S...-WESTCH (Reel 5374, Frame 876-902)
    - WESTERL (Reel 5374, Frame 879-880; 895)
    - WESTERN A...-WESTERN R... (Reel 5374, Frame 808-820)
    - WESTERN A...-WESTERN R..., cont. (Reel 5374, Frame 881-894)
    - WESTF-WESTIN (Reel 5374, Frame 896-903)
    - Westinghouse, 1969-1980 (Reel 5374, Frame 904-926)
    - Westmoreland Co. [Pa.] Museum of Art, 1960-1980 (Reel 5374, Frame 927-994)
    - WESTO-WHE (Reel 5374, Frame 995-1059)
    - WHIP-WHITE P... (Reel 5374, Frame 1060-1109)
    - White, Robert, 1960-1981 (Reel 5374, Frame 1110-1237)
    - WHITE, S.-WHITNEY, E. (Reel 5374, Frame 1238-1258)
    - Whitney, John H., 1948-1971 (Reel 5374, Frame 1259-1274)
    - Whitney, K., 1976 (Reel 5374, Frame 1275-1276)
    - Whitney Museum, 1933-1952 (Reel 5374, Frame 1277-1545)
    - Whitney Museum, cont., 1953-1975, undated (Reel 5375, Frame 5-191)
    - WHITNEY P...-WHY (Reel 5375, Frame 192-216)
    - Wichita Art Association, 1939-1978 (Reel 5375, Frame 217-253)
    - WICHITA N...-WID (Reel 5375, Frame 254-270)
    - WIE-WIK (Reel 5375, Frame 271-334)
    - WILB-WILK (Reel 5375, Frame 335-412)
    - WILLA-WILLO (Reel 5375, Frame 413-488)
    - William Rockhill Nelson Gallery of Art (see: Nelson, William Rockhill, Gallery of Art) (Reel 5375)
    - Williams College (see: Lawrence Art Museum) (Reel 5375)
    - Wilmington Society of the Fine Arts, 1939-1969 (Reel 5375, Frame 489-543)
    - Wilmotte, Raymond M., 1945-1947 (Reel 5375, Frame 544-578)
    - WILSON, C.-WILSON, Y. (Reel 5375, Frame 579-631)
    - Window Displays (see also: Decoration, Interior and Window Display), 1941-1950 (Reel 5375, Frame 632-651)
    - WINE-WISCONSIN, UNIVERSITY OF [GREEN BAY] (Reel 5375, Frame 652-684)
    - Wisconsin, University of [Madison], 1943-1973 (Reel 5375, Frame 685-765)
    - WISCONSIN, UNIVERSITY OF [SUPERIOR]-WISE, G. (Reel 5375, Frame 766-788)
    - Wise, William H., 1954-1972, undated (Reel 5375, Frame 807-1114)
    - WISEM-WITTE (Reel 5375, Frame 789-806)
    - Witte Memorial Museum, 1943-1956 (Reel 5375, Frame 1115-1185)
    - WITTEN-WOLF, H. (Reel 5375, Frame 1186-1245)
    - WOLF, J.-WOLF, W. (Reel 5375, Frame 1246-1276)
    - WOLFE-WOLK (Reel 5375, Frame 1277-1333)
    - WOM-WON (Reel 5375, Frame 1334-1383)
    - WOOD, A.-WOOD, L. (Reel 5375, Frame 1384-1408)
    - Wood, Rawson L., 1957-1972 (Reel 5375, Frame 1409-1445)
    - WOOD, RI...-WOOS (Reel 5375, Frame 1446-1476)
    - Worcester Art Museum, 1937-1948 (Reel 5375, Frame 1477-1562)
    - Worcester Art Museum, cont., 1948-1968 (Reel 5376, Frame 5-39)
    - Workman, David T., 1960-1975, undated (Reel 5376, Frame 40-146)
    - WORKS (Reel 5376, Frame 147-151)
    - WORLD C...-WORLD O... (Reel 5376, Frame 152-156)
    - World's Fair, 1962-1964 (Reel 5376, Frame 157-203)
    - WORLDW-WORLE (Reel 5376, Frame 204-206)
    - Wormley, Edward J., 1949-1976 (Reel 5376, Frame 207-247)
    - WORN-WORT (Reel 5376, Frame 248-258)
    - WQ-WYOMING P... (Reel 5376, Frame 259-333)
    - Wyoming, University of (Reel 5376, Frame 334-354)
    - WYS (Reel 5376, Frame 355-356)
    - X (Reel 5376, Frame 357-366)
    - YAK-YAN (Reel 5376, Frame 367-385)
    - Yankee, Inc., 1968-1977 (Reel 5376, Frame 386-450)
    - YANKO-YOUNGK (Reel 5376, Frame 451-495)
    - Young Men's/Young Women's Hebrew Association [N.J., N.Y., and Pa.], 1959-1967 (Reel 5376, Frame 494-537)
    - YOUNK-Z (Reel 5376, Frame 496; 538-631)
    - Unidentified and Illegible (Reel 5376, Frame 632-761)
  - Artists Correspondence, 1927-1989, undated, 1.2:
    Artist correspondence (13.5 linear feet) includes items that are both official and personal in nature because the Gruskins were close friends of many artists represented by Midtown Galleries.
    - Abel, Louise, 1934-1935 (Reel 5376, Frame 765-775)
    - Adler, M. H., 1938, undated (Reel 5376, Frame 776-784)
    - Aldrich, M. Azzi, 1935-1942 (Reel 5376, Frame 785-807)
    - Bartle, Annette, 1957-1966 (Reel 5376, Frame 808-901)
    - Belle, Cecile, 1947-1968, undated (Reel 5376, Frame 902-1039)
    - Berman, Saul, 1932-1947, undated (Reel 5376, Frame 1040-1104)
    - Betts, Edward, 1959-1968 (Reel 5376, Frame 1105-1569)
    - Betts, Edward, cont., 1968-1980 (Reel 5377, Frame 5-547)
    - Billings, Henry, 1946-1972, undated (Reel 5377, Frame 548-656)
    - Binford, Julien, 1940-1951 (Reel 5377, Frame 657-1111)
    - Binford, Julien, cont., 1951-1975, undated (Reel 5378, Frame 5-269)
    - Bishop, Isabel, 1934-1970 (Reel 5378, Frame 270-1090)
    - Bishop, Isabel, cont., 1970-1981, undated (Reel 5379, Frame 5-970)
    - Boss, Homer, 1932-1963, undated (Reel 5379, Frame 971-1023)
    - Bowden, Priscilla, 1973-1974, undated (Reel 5379, Frame 1024-1046)
    - Boyd, Byron, 1934-1935 (Reel 5379, Frame 1047-1069)
    - Cadmus, Paul, 1936-1950 (Reel 5379, Frame 1069-1551)
    - Cadmus, Paul, cont., 1950-1985, undated (Reel 5380, Frame 5-28)
    - Cadmus, Paul, cont., undated (Reel 5381, Frame 5-28)
    - Citron, Minna, 1934-1944, undated (Reel 5381, Frame 29-237)
    - Clark, Fletcher, 1936-1937 (Reel 5381, Frame 238-252)
    - Clemens, Paul, 1943-1951, undated (Reel 5381, Frame 253-386)
    - Cobb, Ruth, 1973-1984 (Reel 5381, Frame 387-488)
    - Coiner, Charles, 1963-1979, undated (Reel 5381, Frame 489-1036)
    - Criss, Francis, 1934-1938, undated (Reel 5381, Frame 1037-1068)
    - Cuming, Beatrice, 1934-1938, undated (Reel 5381, Frame 1069-1084)
    - Currie, Bruce, 1983 (Reel 5381, Frame 1085-1106)
    - Custer, Bernardine, 1934-1973, undated (Reel 5381, Frame 1107-1229)
    - Davis, Gladys Rockmore, 1938-1949 (Reel 5381, Frame 1230-1554)
    - Davis, Gladys Rockmore, cont., 1950-1958, undated (Reel 5382, Frame 5-290)
    - De Creeft, Jose, 1957 (Reel 5382, Frame 291-298)
    - De Groot, Adelaide, 1938-1941 (Reel 5382, Frame 299-363)
    - Dehner, Walt, 1934-1935 (Reel 5382, Frame 364-378)
    - Dolnick, Beej, 1976, undated (Reel 5382, Frame 382-403)
    - Drennan, Vincent, 1933-1939, undated (Reel 5382, Frame 404-423)
    - Emerson, Sybil, 1935 (Reel 5382, Frame 424-431)
    - Esner, Arthur, 1967-1973 (Reel 5382, Frame 432-451)
    - Etnier, Stephen, 1974-1983, undated (Reel 5382, Frame 452-743)
    - Etting, Emlen, 1939-1971 (Reel 5382, Frame 744-1559)
    - Etting, Emlen, cont., 1971-1980, undated (Reel 5383, Frame 5-246)
    - Evergood, Philip, 1935-1940, undated (Reel 5383, Frame 247-275)
    - Feigin, Dorothy Lubell, 1933-1937, undated (Reel 5383, Frame 434-462)
    - Ferber, Herbert, 1937-1948, undated (Reel 5383, Frame 463-494)
    - Ferry, Frances, 1934-1936 (Reel 5383, Frame 495-499)
    - Fiene, Ernest, 1958-1968, undated (Reel 5383, Frame 276-433)
    - Fitch, Eugene, 1935 (Reel 5383, Frame 500-502)
    - Freedman, Maurice, 1935-1977, undated (Reel 5383, Frame 503-644)
    - Gerber, M. Soule, 1934-1935 (Reel 5383, Frame 645-651)
    - Gilbert, James J., 1934-1935, undated (Reel 5383, Frame 652-662)
    - Goodman, Bertram, 1932-1935, undated (Reel 5383, Frame 663-692)
    - Grandin, Elizabeth, 1935-1936 (Reel 5383, Frame 693-706)
    - Guston, Philip, 1943-1952, undated (Reel 5383, Frame 707-1060)
    - Hale, Nathan Cabot, 1962-1980, undated (Reel 5383, Frame 1061-1371)
    - Harkavy, Minna, 1937-1955, undated (Reel 5383, Frame 1372-1481)
    - Hine, Eleanor, 1932-1935, undated (Reel 5383, Frame 1482-1508)
    - Howe, Ethel Norton, 1935, undated (Reel 5383, Frame 1509-1523)
    - Howe, Gordon, undated (Reel 5383, Frame 1524-1527)
    - Howland, Isabella, 1950-1952 (Reel 5384, Frame 6-28)
    - Huntington, Margaret, 1933-1939, undated (Reel 5384, Frame 29-71)
    - Hutchinson, Mary, 1933-1939, undated (Reel 5384, Frame 72-127)
    - Katz, Ethel, 1933-1934, undated (Reel 5384, Frame 128-144)
    - Kester, Lenard, 1946-1953, undated (Reel 5384, Frame 245-510)
    - Kingman, Dong, 1941-1954 (Reel 5384, Frame 511-1543)
    - Kingman, Dong, cont., 1954-1958, undated (Reel 5385, Frame 5-720)
    - Koerner, Henry, 1947-1982, undated (Reel 5385, Frame 721-1425)
    - Kraemer, Albert, 1935-1946 (Reel 5385, Frame 1426-1464)
    - Kroth, Richard, 1933-1936 (Reel 5385, Frame 1467-1490)
    - Lahm, Reneé, 1933-1939 (Reel 5385, Frame 1465, 1491-1530)
    - Lahm, Reneé, cont., 1939-1946, undated (Reel 5386, Frame 5-167)
    - Laning, Edward, 1932-1947, undated (Reel 5386, Frame 168-318)
    - Libby, Mark Forester, 1973-1977, undated (Reel 5386, Frame 319-349)
    - Logasa, Charles, 1938 (Reel 5386, Frame 350-535)
    - Loran, Erle, 1946-1949, undated (Reel 5386, Frame 354-369)
    - Magafan, Ethel, 1967-1978, undated (Reel 5386, Frame 370-646)
    - Maladarelli, Oronzio, 1927-1957, undated (Reel 5386, Frame 647-1009)
    - Mangravite, Peppino, 1946-1947 (Reel 5386, Frame 1010-1012)
    - Margulies, Joseph, 1932-1934, undated (Reel 5386, Frame 1013-1032)
    - Marker, William B., 1934-1944, undated (Reel 5386, Frame 1030-1065)
    - Martin, Fletcher, 1937-1942 (Reel 5386, Frame 1066-1517)
    - Martin, Fletcher, cont., 1942-1946, undated (Reel 5387, Frame 5-265)
    - Mason, Nan, 1932-1935, undated (Reel 5387, Frame 266-293)
    - Mayhew, Richard, 1968-1981, undated (Reel 5387, Frame 294-623)
    - Mechau, Frank, 1934-1936, undated (Reel 5387, Frame 624-724)
    - Meltsner, Paul R., 1932-1945, undated (Reel 5387, Frame 725-952)
    - Meyer, Fred, 1946-1974 (Reel 5387, Frame 953-1401)
    - Meyer, Fred, cont., 1945-1974, undated (Reel 5388, Frame 5-87)
    - Miccoli, Arnaldo, 1976, undated (Reel 5388, Frame 88-95)
    - Miles, Lou, 1932-1939, undated (Reel 5388, Frame 96-113)
    - Millet, Thalia, 1936, undated (Reel 5388, Frame 114-125)
    - Miyamoto, K., 1933-1934 (Reel 5388, Frame 126-135)
    - Mock, Gladys, 1933-1934 (Reel 5388, Frame 136-142)
    - Moller, Hans, 1963-1978, undated (Reel 5388, Frame 143-639)
    - Mommer, Paul, 1935-1938, undated (Reel 5388, Frame 640-679)
    - Morton, Geer, 1976, undated (Reel 5388, Frame 680-709)
    - Moyer, Roy, 1966-1975, undated (Reel 5388, Frame 710-775)
    - Nagler, Edith, 1933-1972, undated (Reel 5388, Frame 776-813)
    - Nagler, Fred, 1936-1974 (Reel 5388, Frame 814-1490)
    - Nagler, Fred, cont., 1974-1977, undated (Reel 5389, Frame 5-76)
    - Oddo, Alfonso, 1933 (Reel 5389, Frame 77-79)
    - Oppenheimer, Selma L., 1936-1937, undated (Reel 5389, Frame 80-96)
    - Palmer, William, 1943-1976, undated (Reel 5389, Frame 97-1044)
    - Parsons, Betty Pierson, 1935-1959, undated (Reel 5389, Frame 1045-1213)
    - Peirce, Alzira, 1938-1949, undated (Reel 5389, Frame 1214-1374)
    - Peirce, Waldo, 1932-1936 (Reel 5389, Frame 1375-1530)
    - Peirce, Waldo, cont., 1937-1959 (Reel 5390, Frame 5-1565)
    - Peirce, Waldo, cont., 1959-1977, undated (Reel 5391, Frame 5-907)
    - Pierce, Henry Jr., 1935 (Reel 5391, Frame 908-910)
    - Puccinelli, Raimondo, 1958-1966, undated (Reel 5391, Frame 911-1020)
    - Rees, Rosalie, 1932-1941 (Reel 5391, Frame 1021-1029)
    - Reinhardt, Siegfried, 1959-1973, undated (Reel 5391, Frame 1085-1331)
    - Reiss, Lionel S., 1938-1945, undated (Reel 5391, Frame 1030-1084)
    - Rosenthal, Doris, 1935-1943 (Reel 5391, Frame 1332-1558)
    - Rosenthal, Doris, cont., 1943-1972 (Reel 5392, Frame 5-1541)
    - Rosenthal, Doris, cont., 1972-1979 (Reel 5393, Frame 5-597)
    - Saarinen, Lilian, 1943-1956, undated (Reel 5393, Frame 598-873)
    - Saul (see: Berman) (Reel 5393)
    - Schein, Eugenie, 1935-1938, undated (Reel 5393, Frame 874-876)
    - Schoener, Jason, 1956-1980, undated (Reel 5393, Frame 877-1511)
    - Sepeshy, Zoltan, 1938 (Reel 5393, Frame 1512-1555)
    - Sepeshy, Zoltan, cont., 1938-1974, undated (Reel 5394, Frame 5-1448)
    - Shaw, Harry H., 1932 (Reel 5394, Frame 1449-1458)
    - Sheets, Nan, 1938-1939 (Reel 5394, Frame 1459-1472)
    - Shulkin, Anatol, 1935-1956 (Reel 5394, Frame 1473-1568)
    - Shulkin, Anatol, cont., 1956-1967 (Reel 5395, Frame 5-134)
    - Simkhovitch, Simka, 1940-1951, undated (Reel 5395, Frame 135-266)
    - Simpson, Martha, 1935-1937, undated (Reel 5395, Frame 267-288)
    - Sivard, Robert, 1954-1977 (Reel 5395, Frame 289-901)
    - Skofield, Raymond W., 1933-1934 (Reel 5395, Frame 902-905)
    - Smith, Jacob Getlar, 1937-1949, undated (Reel 5395, Frame 906-1025)
    - Sokole, Miron, 1934-1962, undated (Reel 5395, Frame 1026-1236)
    - Soyer, Isaac, 1936-1956 (Reel 5395, Frame 1237-1384)
    - Spagna, Vincent, 1936-1944, undated (Reel 5395, Frame 1385-1438)
    - Stillman, Ary, 1934 (Reel 5395, Frame 1439-1467)
    - Taubes, Frederic, 1936-1937 (Reel 5395, Frame 1468-1551)
    - Taubes, Frederic, cont., 1937-1942, undated (Reel 5396, Frame 5-1222)
    - Teague, Louis, 1951-1953 (Reel 5396, Frame 1223-1230)
    - Thon, William, 1948-1957 (Reel 5396, Frame 1231-1556)
    - Thon, William, cont., 1957-1978, undated (Reel 5397, Frame 5-672)
    - Thorwald, Clara, 1934, undated (Reel 5397, Frame 673-675)
    - Varga, Margit, 1934-1981, undated (Reel 5397, Frame 676-812)
    - Vickrey, Robert, 1952-1968 (Reel 5397, Frame 813-1538)
    - Vickrey, Robert, cont., 1968-1982, undated (Reel 5398, Frame 5-1559)
    - Vickrey, Robert, cont., undated (Reel 5399, Frame 5-36)
    - Vukovic, Marko, 1933-1936, undated (Reel 5399, Frame 37-69)
    - Wessels, Helen, 1932-1934, undated (Reel 5399, Frame 70-78)
    - Wiltz, Arnold, 1935-1937, undated (Reel 5399, Frame 79-92)
    - Wingate, Arline, 1938-1960, undated (Reel 5399, Frame 93-292)
    - Wolfson, Paula, 1973-1975, undated (Reel 5399, Frame 293-317)
    - Young, E. Helen, 1934-1942, undated (Reel 5399, Frame 318-332)
  - Artist Applications, 1932-1972, 1.3:
    Artist applications (0.5 linear feet) contain correspondence with artists interested in affiliating with Midtown Galleries. These files include both accepted and rejected applicants.
    - Artist Applications, A (Reel 5399, Frame 335-423)
    - Artist Applications, B (Reel 5399, Frame 424-561)
    - Artist Applications, C (Reel 5399, Frame 562-667)
    - Artist Applications, D (Reel 5399, Frame 668-812)
    - Artist Applications, E (Reel 5399, Frame 813-855)
    - Artist Applications, F (Reel 5399, Frame 856-932)
    - Artist Applications, G (Reel 5399, Frame 933-1037)
    - Artist Applications, H (Reel 5399, Frame 1038-1113)
    - Artist Applications, I-J (Reel 5399, Frame 1114-1147)
    - Artist Applications, K (Reel 5399, Frame 1148-1265)
    - Artist Applications, L (Reel 5399, Frame 1266-1377)
    - Artist Applications, M (Reel 5400, Frame 6-140)
    - Artist Applications, N-O (Reel 5400, Frame 141-192)
    - Artist Applications, P-Q (Reel 5400, Frame 193-282)
    - Artist Applications, R (Reel 5400, Frame 283-377)
    - Artist Applications, SA-SL (Reel 5400, Frame 378-510)
    - Artist Applications, SM-SZ (Reel 5400, Frame 511-609)
    - Artist Applications, T-V (Reel 5400, Frame 610-686)
    - Artist Applications, W (Reel 5400, Frame 687-811)
    - Artist Applications, X-Y-Z (Reel 5400, Frame 812-835)
- Exhibitions, 1932-1982, undated, Series 2:; (4 linear feet)
  The Exhibitions series includes schedules and information about traveling shows, which were usually group exhibitions built around themes; these records are arranged chronologically. The majority of the records in this series consist of files on particular exhibitions, including both traveling shows and exhibitions held at Midtown Galleries; these records are arranged alphabetically by exhibition title. See the Appendix for a chronological list of Midtown Galleries exhibitions.
  The series is organized into two subsseries:
  2.1: Schedules and General Correspondence, 1932-1982, undated
  2.2: Midtown Galleries Exhibition Files, A-Z, 1934-1982, undated
  - Schedules and General Correspondence, 1932-1982, undated, 2.1: